{
    "subject": "resource/Sidney_Toler",
    "predicate": "ontology/activeYearsStartYear",
    "object": "1903",
    "human_readable": "Sidney Toler started his acting career in 1903.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9723846912384033,
            "question": "When did Sidney Toler begin his acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134978652000427,
            "question": "In what year did Sidney Toler start acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8985998034477234,
            "question": "Was Sidney Toler's acting career successful?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8878989219665527,
            "question": "What decade did Sidney Toler begin his acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7542147040367126,
            "question": "What was Sidney Toler's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6493067741394043,
            "question": "Is Sidney Toler known for any particular roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5953961610794067,
            "question": "What type of entertainment was Sidney Toler involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5454605221748352,
            "question": "Did Sidney Toler win any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4759996235370636,
            "question": "How long did Sidney Toler work as an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22068552672863007,
            "question": "What were some of Sidney Toler's most famous films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sidney Toler started his acting career in 1903.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1958_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long did Sidney Toler work as an actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1958_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Sidney Toler win any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1958_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of entertainment was Sidney Toler involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1958_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1958_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention that Sidney Toler started his acting career on the stage before moving into films, but they do not specify the exact year. However, one document mentions that he made his own transition into the movies in 1929, which implies that his acting career started before then. There is no information to suggest that he started his acting career in 1903."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention any information about Sidney Toler starting his acting career in 1903. According to the documents, Sidney Toler began his acting career on the stage and later moved into early talking films, but there is no specific mention of the year 1903 as the beginning of his acting career."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}